{"name": "Childhood Cancer Late Effect", "children": [{"name": "Cancer", "children": [{"name": "Melanoma", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with melanoma?", "name": "melanoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0025202"}]}]}, {"name": "Angiosarcoma", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Hemangiosarcoma?", "name": "Hemangiosarcoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0018923"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Angiosarcoma of liver?", "name": "Angiosarcoma of liver", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0345907"}]}]}, {"name": "Adrenocortical Carcinoma", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Adrenocortical carcinoma?", "name": "Adrenocortical carcinoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0206686"}]}]}, {"name": "Retinoblastoma", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Retinoblastoma?", "name": "Retinoblastoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0035335"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Intraocular retinoblastoma?", "name": "Intraocular retinoblastoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0278717"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Extraocular retinoblastoma?", "name": "Extraocular retinoblastoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0278719"}]}]}, {"name": "PTLD", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Post-transplant lymphoproliferative disorder?", "name": "Post-transplant lymphoproliferative disorder", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0432487"}]}]}, {"name": "Pheochromocytoma", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Pheochromocytoma?", "name": "Pheochromocytoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0031511"}]}]}, {"name": "Central Nervous System Neoplasms", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Central Nervous System Neoplasms?", "name": "Central Nervous System Neoplasms", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0085136"}]}]}, {"name": "Germ Cell Tumor", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Teratoma?", "name": "Teratoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0039538"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Teratocarcinoma?", "name": "Teratocarcinoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0206664"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Germinoma?", "name": "Germinoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0206660"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Germ cell tumor?", "name": "Germ cell tumor", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0205851"}]}]}, {"name": "Neuroblastoma", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Neuroblastoma?", "name": "Neuroblastoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0027819"}]}]}, {"name": "Leukemia", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Juvenile Myelomonocytic Leukemia?", "name": "Juvenile Myelomonocytic Leukemia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0349639"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Acute Myeloid Leukemia (AML-M2)?", "name": "Acute Myeloid Leukemia (AML-M2)", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1879321"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with PRE-B-CELL ACUTE LYMPHOBLASTIC LEUKEMIA (allelic variant)?", "name": "PRE-B-CELL ACUTE LYMPHOBLASTIC LEUKEMIA (allelic variant)", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C2700506"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Acute Myeloid Leukemia, M1?", "name": "Acute Myeloid Leukemia, M1", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0026998"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with T-cell childhood acute lymphoblastic leukemia?", "name": "T-cell childhood acute lymphoblastic leukemia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0279583"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with B-cell childhood acute lymphoblastic leukemia?", "name": "B-cell childhood acute lymphoblastic leukemia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0279584"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Acute Promyelocytic Leukemia?", "name": "Acute Promyelocytic Leukemia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0023487"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with leukemia?", "name": "leukemia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0023418"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Acute Megakaryocytic Leukemias?", "name": "Acute Megakaryocytic Leukemias", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0023462"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Acute monocytic leukemia?", "name": "Acute monocytic leukemia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0023465"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Leukemia, Myelocytic, Acute?", "name": "Leukemia, Myelocytic, Acute", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0023467"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with LEUKEMIA, ACUTE MYELOID, M0 SUBTYPE?", "name": "LEUKEMIA, ACUTE MYELOID, M0 SUBTYPE", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1835434"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Myeloid Leukemia, Chronic?", "name": "Myeloid Leukemia, Chronic", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0023473"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Acute myelomonocytic leukemia?", "name": "Acute myelomonocytic leukemia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0023479"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Acute Erythroblastic Leukemia?", "name": "Acute Erythroblastic Leukemia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0023440"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Acute lymphocytic leukemia?", "name": "Acute lymphocytic leukemia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0023449"}]}]}, {"name": "Soft Tissue Sarcomas", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with liposarcoma?", "name": "liposarcoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0023827"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with hemangiopericytoma?", "name": "hemangiopericytoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0018922"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Malignant Fibrous Histiocytoma?", "name": "Malignant Fibrous Histiocytoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0334463"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Botryoid rhabdomyosarcoma?", "name": "Botryoid rhabdomyosarcoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1306574"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with synovial sarcoma?", "name": "synovial sarcoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0039101"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Fibrosarcoma?", "name": "Fibrosarcoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0016057"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Rhabdomyosarcoma?", "name": "Rhabdomyosarcoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0035412"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Bone neoplasms?", "name": "Bone neoplasms", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0005967"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with leiomyosarcoma?", "name": "leiomyosarcoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0023269"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Sarcoma, Spindle Cell?", "name": "Sarcoma, Spindle Cell", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0205945"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Malignant Peripheral Nerve Sheath Tumor?", "name": "Malignant Peripheral Nerve Sheath Tumor", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0751690"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Rhabdomyosarcoma, Embryonal?", "name": "Rhabdomyosarcoma, Embryonal", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0206656"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Alveolar Soft Part Sarcoma?", "name": "Alveolar Soft Part Sarcoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0206657"}]}]}, {"name": "Vascular Tumor", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Vascular Neoplasms?", "name": "Vascular Neoplasms", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0282607"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Hemangioendothelioma, Epithelioid?", "name": "Hemangioendothelioma, Epithelioid", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0206732"}]}]}, {"name": "Nasopharyngeal Carcinoma", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Nasopharyngeal carcinoma?", "name": "Nasopharyngeal carcinoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C2931822"}]}]}, {"name": "Lymphoma", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Hodgkin's disease, nodular sclerosis (clinical)?", "name": "Hodgkin's disease, nodular sclerosis (clinical)", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0152268"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Hodgkin lymphoma, lymphocyte depletion?", "name": "Hodgkin lymphoma, lymphocyte depletion", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0152267"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Mixed Cellularity Hodgkin Lymphoma?", "name": "Mixed Cellularity Hodgkin Lymphoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0152266"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with childhood large cell lymphoma?", "name": "childhood large cell lymphoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0281710"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with B-Cell Lymphomas?", "name": "B-Cell Lymphomas", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0079731"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Nodular Lymphocyte Predominant Hodgkin Lymphoma?", "name": "Nodular Lymphocyte Predominant Hodgkin Lymphoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1334968"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Burkitt-like lymphoma?", "name": "Burkitt-like lymphoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1368771"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Hodgkin Disease?", "name": "Hodgkin Disease", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0019829"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Lymphocyte Rich Classical Hodgkin Lymphoma?", "name": "Lymphocyte Rich Classical Hodgkin Lymphoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1266194"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Lymphoma?", "name": "Lymphoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0024299"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Classical Hodgkin's Lymphoma?", "name": "Classical Hodgkin's Lymphoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1333064"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Precursor cell lymphoblastic lymphoma?", "name": "Precursor cell lymphoblastic lymphoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0079748"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Diffuse Large B-Cell Lymphoma?", "name": "Diffuse Large B-Cell Lymphoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0079744"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Burkitt Lymphoma?", "name": "Burkitt Lymphoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0006413"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Childhood Anaplastic Large Cell Lymphoma?", "name": "Childhood Anaplastic Large Cell Lymphoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1332942"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Lymphoma, Non-Hodgkin?", "name": "Lymphoma, Non-Hodgkin", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0024305"}]}]}, {"name": "Cervical Cancer", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Cervix carcinoma?", "name": "Cervix carcinoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0302592"}]}]}, {"name": "Brain Cancer", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Medulloblastoma?", "name": "Medulloblastoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0025149"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Astrocytoma?", "name": "Astrocytoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0004114"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Ependymoma?", "name": "Ependymoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0014474"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Malignant neoplasm of brain?", "name": "Malignant neoplasm of brain", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0153633"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Glioma of brainstem?", "name": "Glioma of brainstem", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0677865"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Optic Nerve Glioma?", "name": "Optic Nerve Glioma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0346326"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Craniopharyngioma?", "name": "Craniopharyngioma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0010276"}]}]}, {"name": "Neuroendocrine Tumors", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Neuroendocrine Tumors?", "name": "Neuroendocrine Tumors", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0206754"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Carcinoid Tumor?", "name": "Carcinoid Tumor", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0007095"}]}]}, {"name": "Parotid gland neoplasms", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Parotid Neoplasms?", "name": "Parotid Neoplasms", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0030581"}]}]}, {"name": "Liver Tumor", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Liver neoplasms?", "name": "Liver neoplasms", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0023903"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Hepatoblastoma?", "name": "Hepatoblastoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0206624"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with childhood hepatocellular carcinoma?", "name": "childhood hepatocellular carcinoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0279606"}]}]}, {"name": "Thyroid Cancer", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Thyroid carcinoma?", "name": "Thyroid carcinoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0549473"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Medullary carcinoma of thyroid?", "name": "Medullary carcinoma of thyroid", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0238462"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Papillary thyroid carcinoma?", "name": "Papillary thyroid carcinoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0238463"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Anaplastic thyroid carcinoma?", "name": "Anaplastic thyroid carcinoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0238461"}]}]}, {"name": "Bone Tumor", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Ewings sarcoma?", "name": "Ewings sarcoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0553580"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Ewings sarcoma-primitive neuroectodermal tumor (PNET)?", "name": "Ewings sarcoma-primitive neuroectodermal tumor (PNET)", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0684337"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Giant Cell Tumors?", "name": "Giant Cell Tumors", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0017525"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Askin's tumor?", "name": "Askin's tumor", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0877849"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Extraosseous Ewings sarcoma-primitive neuroepithelial tumor?", "name": "Extraosseous Ewings sarcoma-primitive neuroepithelial tumor", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0279980"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Osteosarcoma?", "name": "Osteosarcoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0029463"}]}]}, {"name": "Kidney Tumor", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Rhabdoid Tumor?", "name": "Rhabdoid Tumor", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0206743"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Nephroblastoma?", "name": "Nephroblastoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0027708"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Clear cell sarcoma of kidney?", "name": "Clear cell sarcoma of kidney", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0334488"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Kidney Neoplasm?", "name": "Kidney Neoplasm", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0022665"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Mesoblastic Nephroma?", "name": "Mesoblastic Nephroma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0206628"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Renal Cell Carcinoma?", "name": "Renal Cell Carcinoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0007134"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with neuroepithelial tumor of the kidney?", "name": "neuroepithelial tumor of the kidney", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1134517"}]}]}, {"name": "Solid Tumors", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Solid tumour?", "name": "Solid tumour", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0280100"}]}]}, {"name": "Neurofibromatosis", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Neurofibromatoses?", "name": "Neurofibromatoses", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0162678"}]}]}, {"name": "BPDCN", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Blastic plasmacytoid dendritic cell neoplasm?", "name": "Blastic plasmacytoid dendritic cell neoplasm", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1301363"}]}]}, {"name": "Histiocytosis", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Malignant histiocytosis?", "name": "Malignant histiocytosis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0019623"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Histiocytosis, Langerhans-Cell?", "name": "Histiocytosis, Langerhans-Cell", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0019621"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Histiocytosis?", "name": "Histiocytosis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0019618"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Monocytic leukemia?", "name": "Monocytic leukemia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0598894"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Was this patient diagnosed with Lymphohistiocytosis, Hemophagocytic?", "name": "Lymphohistiocytosis, Hemophagocytic", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0024291"}]}]}]}, {"name": "Late Effect", "children": [{"name": "Digestive System", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Malabsorption Syndrome?", "name": "Malabsorption Syndrome", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0024523"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Esophageal Stenosis?", "name": "Esophageal Stenosis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0014866"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Gastrointestinal toxicity?", "name": "Gastrointestinal toxicity", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1142499"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Gall Bladder Diseases?", "name": "Gall Bladder Diseases", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0016977"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Chronic enterocolitis?", "name": "Chronic enterocolitis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C2242689"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Intestinal Obstruction?", "name": "Intestinal Obstruction", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0021843"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Cholelithiasis?", "name": "Cholelithiasis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0008350"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Nodular hyperplasia?", "name": "Nodular hyperplasia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0020510"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Stomach ache?", "name": "Stomach ache", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0221512"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Hepatitis C?", "name": "Hepatitis C", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0019196"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Diabetes Mellitus?", "name": "Diabetes Mellitus", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0011849"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Hepatitis B?", "name": "Hepatitis B", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0019163"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Microvesicular fat disease of liver?", "name": "Microvesicular fat disease of liver", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0860214"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Liver Cirrhosis?", "name": "Liver Cirrhosis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0023890"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Insulin Resistance?", "name": "Insulin Resistance", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0021655"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Hepatotoxicity?", "name": "Hepatotoxicity", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0235378"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Intestinal adhesions with obstruction?", "name": "Intestinal adhesions with obstruction", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0267478"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Fecal Incontinence?", "name": "Fecal Incontinence", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0015732"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Fibrosis, Liver?", "name": "Fibrosis, Liver", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0239946"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Steatohepatitis?", "name": "Steatohepatitis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C2711227"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Focal Nodular Hyperplasia?", "name": "Focal Nodular Hyperplasia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0333980"}]}]}, {"name": "Chronic Pain", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Chronic pain?", "name": "Chronic pain", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0150055"}]}]}, {"name": "Respiratory System", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Wheezing?", "name": "Wheezing", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0043144"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Lung Diseases, Obstructive?", "name": "Lung Diseases, Obstructive", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0600260"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Pneumonia, Interstitial?", "name": "Pneumonia, Interstitial", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0206061"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Pneumonia?", "name": "Pneumonia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0032285"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of FVC - forced vital capacity abnormal?", "name": "FVC - forced vital capacity abnormal", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0580372"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Coughing?", "name": "Coughing", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0010200"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Pleurisy?", "name": "Pleurisy", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0032231"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Bronchiolitis Obliterans?", "name": "Bronchiolitis Obliterans", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0006272"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Pulmonary Fibrosis?", "name": "Pulmonary Fibrosis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0034069"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Pulmonary Veno-Occlusive Disease (disorder)?", "name": "Pulmonary Veno-Occlusive Disease (disorder)", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0034091"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Restrictive lung disease?", "name": "Restrictive lung disease", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0085581"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of acute pneumonitis?", "name": "acute pneumonitis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C2215251"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Bronchitis, Chronic?", "name": "Bronchitis, Chronic", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0008677"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Bronchiectasis?", "name": "Bronchiectasis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0006267"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Pulmonary Dysfunction?", "name": "Pulmonary Dysfunction", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1709770"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Dyspnea?", "name": "Dyspnea", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0013404"}]}]}, {"name": "Endocrine System", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Fasting hyperglycaemia?", "name": "Fasting hyperglycaemia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C2609269"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Dyslipidemias?", "name": "Dyslipidemias", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0242339"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Adrenocorticotropic hormone (ACTH) deficiency (disorder)?", "name": "Adrenocorticotropic hormone (ACTH) deficiency (disorder)", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0342388"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Hypertensive disease?", "name": "Hypertensive disease", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0020538"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Glucose metabolism abnormal?", "name": "Glucose metabolism abnormal", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1142273"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Hypogonadotropic hypogonadism?", "name": "Hypogonadotropic hypogonadism", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0271623"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Endocrine abnormalities of gonadal function NEC?", "name": "Endocrine abnormalities of gonadal function NEC", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0851788"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Precocious Puberty?", "name": "Precocious Puberty", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0034013"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Hyperprolactinemia?", "name": "Hyperprolactinemia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0020514"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Hyperinsulinism?", "name": "Hyperinsulinism", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0020459"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Secondary Adrenal Insufficiency?", "name": "Secondary Adrenal Insufficiency", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0948387"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Pituitary dwarfism?", "name": "Pituitary dwarfism", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0013338"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Hypothyroidism?", "name": "Hypothyroidism", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0020676"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Obesity?", "name": "Obesity", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0028754"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Metabolic Syndrome X?", "name": "Metabolic Syndrome X", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0524620"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Hyperthyroidism?", "name": "Hyperthyroidism", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0020550"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Thyroid dysfunction?", "name": "Thyroid dysfunction", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0348024"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Thyroid Nodule?", "name": "Thyroid Nodule", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0040137"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Diabetes Mellitus, Non-Insulin-Dependent?", "name": "Diabetes Mellitus, Non-Insulin-Dependent", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0011860"}]}]}, {"name": "Immune System", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Conjunctivitis?", "name": "Conjunctivitis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0009763"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Sinusitis?", "name": "Sinusitis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0037199"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of T-cell dysfunction?", "name": "T-cell dysfunction", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C3277427"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Bronchitis?", "name": "Bronchitis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0006277"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Hyposplenia?", "name": "Hyposplenia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1834932"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Secretory Component Deficiency?", "name": "Secretory Component Deficiency", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0398709"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Decreased B cells?", "name": "Decreased B cells", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1837337"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Post-splenectomy septicemia?", "name": "Post-splenectomy septicemia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0472810"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Hypogammaglobulinemia?", "name": "Hypogammaglobulinemia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0086438"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Graft-vs-Host Disease?", "name": "Graft-vs-Host Disease", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0018133"}]}]}, {"name": "Occular", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Orbital Margin, Hypoplasia of?", "name": "Orbital Margin, Hypoplasia of", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1833795"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Diabetic optic papillopathy?", "name": "Diabetic optic papillopathy", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1275499"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Enophthalmos?", "name": "Enophthalmos", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0014306"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Disorder of macula of retina?", "name": "Disorder of macula of retina", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0730362"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Keratitis?", "name": "Keratitis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0022568"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Glaucoma?", "name": "Glaucoma", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0017601"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Xerophthalmia?", "name": "Xerophthalmia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0043349"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Telangiectasis?", "name": "Telangiectasis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0039446"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Retinal Diseases?", "name": "Retinal Diseases", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0035309"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Cataract?", "name": "Cataract", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0086543"}]}]}, {"name": "Musculoskeletal System", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Amputation?", "name": "Amputation", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0002688"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Kyphosis deformity of spine?", "name": "Kyphosis deformity of spine", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0022821"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Cartilaginous exostosis?", "name": "Cartilaginous exostosis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0029423"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Contracture of joint?", "name": "Contracture of joint", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0009918"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Osteoporosis?", "name": "Osteoporosis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0029456"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Fracture?", "name": "Fracture", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0016658"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Bone necrosis?", "name": "Bone necrosis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0029445"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Fibrosis?", "name": "Fibrosis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0016059"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Hypoplasia?", "name": "Hypoplasia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0243069"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Scoliosis due to radiation?", "name": "Scoliosis due to radiation", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0158504"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Craniofacial Abnormalities?", "name": "Craniofacial Abnormalities", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0376634"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Disfigurement?", "name": "Disfigurement", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1707791"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Avascular necrosis of bone?", "name": "Avascular necrosis of bone", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0027543"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of abnormal growth?", "name": "abnormal growth", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0262361"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Decreased joint mobility?", "name": "Decreased joint mobility", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1857108"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Scoliosis, unspecified?", "name": "Scoliosis, unspecified", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0036439"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Limb length discrepancy?", "name": "Limb length discrepancy", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0410785"}]}]}, {"name": "Reproductive System", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Congenital Abnormality?", "name": "Congenital Abnormality", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0000768"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Fertility problem?", "name": "Fertility problem", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0278048"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Premature Menopause?", "name": "Premature Menopause", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0025322"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Infertility?", "name": "Infertility", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0021359"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Gonadal Disorders?", "name": "Gonadal Disorders", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0018050"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Retrograde ejaculation?", "name": "Retrograde ejaculation", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0403673"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Ovarian Failure, Premature?", "name": "Ovarian Failure, Premature", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0085215"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Oligospermia?", "name": "Oligospermia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0028960"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Sexual Dysfunction?", "name": "Sexual Dysfunction", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0549622"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Azoospermia?", "name": "Azoospermia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0004509"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Cancer Risk?", "name": "Cancer Risk", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0596244"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Amenorrhea?", "name": "Amenorrhea", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0002453"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Hereditary Diseases?", "name": "Hereditary Diseases", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0019247"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Erectile dysfunction?", "name": "Erectile dysfunction", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0242350"}]}]}, {"name": "Urinary System", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Renal dysfunction?", "name": "Renal dysfunction", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C3279454"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Urinary Incontinence?", "name": "Urinary Incontinence", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0042024"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Renal Insufficiency?", "name": "Renal Insufficiency", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1565489"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Hyperfiltration focal segmental glomerulosclerosis?", "name": "Hyperfiltration focal segmental glomerulosclerosis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0403427"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Chronic urinary tract infection?", "name": "Chronic urinary tract infection", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0262421"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Vesico-Ureteral Reflux?", "name": "Vesico-Ureteral Reflux", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0042580"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Hemorrhagic cystitis?", "name": "Hemorrhagic cystitis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0085692"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Dysfunctional voiding?", "name": "Dysfunctional voiding", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0403659"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Fibrosis of urinary bladder?", "name": "Fibrosis of urinary bladder", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0521626"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Fanconi Syndrome?", "name": "Fanconi Syndrome", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0015624"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of kidney; damage?", "name": "kidney; damage", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1408258"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Hydrocele male?", "name": "Hydrocele male", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0859074"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Hydronephrosis?", "name": "Hydronephrosis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0020295"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Renal hypertension?", "name": "Renal hypertension", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0020544"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Urinary tract obstruction?", "name": "Urinary tract obstruction", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0178879"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Urinary Calculi?", "name": "Urinary Calculi", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0042018"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Proteinuria?", "name": "Proteinuria", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0033687"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Renal tubular acidosis?", "name": "Renal tubular acidosis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0001126"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Hypophosphatemic Rickets?", "name": "Hypophosphatemic Rickets", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1704375"}]}]}, {"name": "Fatigue", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Fatigue?", "name": "Fatigue", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0015672"}]}]}, {"name": "Central Nervous System", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Mental Depression?", "name": "Mental Depression", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0011570"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Poor short-term memory?", "name": "Poor short-term memory", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0701811"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Impaired long-term verbal memory?", "name": "Impaired long-term verbal memory", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1841624"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Gait Ataxia?", "name": "Gait Ataxia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0751837"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Papilledema?", "name": "Papilledema", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0030353"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Sensory deficit?", "name": "Sensory deficit", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0748618"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Upward gaze paresis?", "name": "Upward gaze paresis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1843866"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Attention Deficit Disorder?", "name": "Attention Deficit Disorder", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0041671"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Impulsive Behavior?", "name": "Impulsive Behavior", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0021125"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Abnormal coordination?", "name": "Abnormal coordination", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0520966"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Learning Disabilities?", "name": "Learning Disabilities", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0751265"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Movement Disorders?", "name": "Movement Disorders", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0026650"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Withdrawn behavior?", "name": "Withdrawn behavior", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0475703"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Ataxia?", "name": "Ataxia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0004134"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Foot-drop?", "name": "Foot-drop", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0085684"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Asthenia?", "name": "Asthenia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0004093"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Nystagmus?", "name": "Nystagmus", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0028738"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Seizures?", "name": "Seizures", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0036572"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Paralysed?", "name": "Paralysed", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0522224"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Optic Atrophy?", "name": "Optic Atrophy", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0029124"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Hemiparesis?", "name": "Hemiparesis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0018989"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Neurogenic Bowel?", "name": "Neurogenic Bowel", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0695242"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of cognitive/functional effects?", "name": "cognitive/functional effects", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0935657"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Paresthesia?", "name": "Paresthesia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0030554"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Attention deficit hyperactivity disorder?", "name": "Attention deficit hyperactivity disorder", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1263846"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder?", "name": "Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0038436"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Absent reflex?", "name": "Absent reflex", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0234146"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Muscle Spasticity?", "name": "Muscle Spasticity", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0026838"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Focal Neurologic Deficits?", "name": "Focal Neurologic Deficits", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0746857"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Cerebellar Diseases?", "name": "Cerebellar Diseases", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0007760"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Visual Motor Coordination?", "name": "Visual Motor Coordination", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0042828"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Muscle hypotonia?", "name": "Muscle hypotonia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0026827"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Hyperactive behavior?", "name": "Hyperactive behavior", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0424295"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Short-term memory impairment?", "name": "Short-term memory impairment", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C2363813"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Dysarthria?", "name": "Dysarthria", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0013362"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Neurogenic Urinary Bladder?", "name": "Neurogenic Urinary Bladder", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0005697"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Cerebellar Dysmetria?", "name": "Cerebellar Dysmetria", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0234162"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Shunt malfunction?", "name": "Shunt malfunction", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0948276"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of motor deficit?", "name": "motor deficit", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0746626"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of psychological distress?", "name": "psychological distress", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0815107"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Moyamoya Disease?", "name": "Moyamoya Disease", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0026654"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Neurologic Effect?", "name": "Neurologic Effect", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1518287"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Hydrocephalus?", "name": "Hydrocephalus", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0020255"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Headache?", "name": "Headache", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0018681"}]}]}, {"name": "Dental Problems", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Xerostomia?", "name": "Xerostomia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0043352"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Malocclusion?", "name": "Malocclusion", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0024636"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Dental caries?", "name": "Dental caries", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0011334"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Enamel dysplasia?", "name": "Enamel dysplasia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1849736"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Microdontia?", "name": "Microdontia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0240340"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Hypodontia?", "name": "Hypodontia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0020608"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Deglutition Disorders?", "name": "Deglutition Disorders", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0011168"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Tooth problem?", "name": "Tooth problem", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0576962"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Osteoradionecrosis?", "name": "Osteoradionecrosis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0029461"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Periodontal Diseases?", "name": "Periodontal Diseases", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0031090"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Malignant neoplasm of mouth?", "name": "Malignant neoplasm of mouth", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0153381"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Maxillary hyperplasia?", "name": "Maxillary hyperplasia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0240309"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Temporomandibular Joint Dysfunction Syndrome?", "name": "Temporomandibular Joint Dysfunction Syndrome", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0039496"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Salivary Gland Diseases?", "name": "Salivary Gland Diseases", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0036093"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Mandibular hyperplasia?", "name": "Mandibular hyperplasia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0302501"}]}]}, {"name": "Secondary Cancer", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Second Primary Cancers?", "name": "Second Primary Cancers", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0751623"}]}]}, {"name": "Auditory", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Conductive hearing loss?", "name": "Conductive hearing loss", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0018777"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Vertigo?", "name": "Vertigo", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0042571"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Deafness?", "name": "Deafness", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0011053"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Diplacusis?", "name": "Diplacusis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0152228"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Tinnitus?", "name": "Tinnitus", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0040264"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Sensorineural Hearing Loss (disorder)?", "name": "Sensorineural Hearing Loss (disorder)", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0018784"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Ototoxicity?", "name": "Ototoxicity", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0235280"}]}]}, {"name": "Cardiovascular", "children": [{"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Myocardial Infarction?", "name": "Myocardial Infarction", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0027051"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of HEART PROBLEM?", "name": "HEART PROBLEM", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0795691"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Vascular System Injuries?", "name": "Vascular System Injuries", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0178324"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Cardiac Arrhythmia?", "name": "Cardiac Arrhythmia", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0003811"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Coronary heart disease?", "name": "Coronary heart disease", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0010068"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Fibrosis of pericardium?", "name": "Fibrosis of pericardium", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0152452"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Myopathy?", "name": "Myopathy", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0026848"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Coronary Arteriosclerosis?", "name": "Coronary Arteriosclerosis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0010054"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Conduction disorder of the heart?", "name": "Conduction disorder of the heart", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0264886"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Cerebrovascular accident?", "name": "Cerebrovascular accident", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0038454"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Congestive heart failure?", "name": "Congestive heart failure", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0018802"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Pericarditis?", "name": "Pericarditis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0031046"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Endocardial Fibroelastosis?", "name": "Endocardial Fibroelastosis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0014117"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Valvular abnormality?", "name": "Valvular abnormality", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0241654"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Pancarditis?", "name": "Pancarditis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0030270"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Pericardial Effusion, Chronic?", "name": "Pericardial Effusion, Chronic", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C1850039"}]}, {"answertype": "radio", "question": "Did this patient ever demonstrate signs of Myocardial fibrosis?", "name": "Myocardial fibrosis", "answers": ["yes", "no"], "triggers": [{"type": "cui", "name": "C0151654"}]}]}]}, {"answertype": "text", "question": "What protocol was this patient put on?", "name": "Protocol", "triggers": [{"type": "keyword", "name": "pog"}, {"type": "keyword", "name": "cog"}, {"type": "keyword", "name": "ccg"}, {"type": "keyword", "name": "protocol"}]}]}